HANNA TISCHER

hannalethtischer@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/hanna-leth-tischer

hannalt.github.io

704-928-7887

About

Hanna Tischer is a thoughtful, ambitious, and creative Tech Specialist with professional leadership experience. Her technical skills are backed by her ability to communicate them. This allows her to lead teams to consistently outperform their goals.

Education

University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill

Expected May 2022

Bachelor of Science (B.S.) in Computer Science

Bachelor of Arts (B.A.) in English, concentration in Creative Writing

GPA: 3.681

Honors

Honors Carolina - Highly competitive, four-year academic program enrolling 10% of each class **Buckley Public Service Scholar** - Four-year fellowship focused on community service **UNC Dean's List** - Spring 2019, Fall 2019, Qualified - Spring 2020, Fall 2020, Spring 2021

Professional Experience

General Electric Gas Power

Atlanta, GA

Experience Digital Technology Intern

May 2021 - August 2021

- Used Tableau to create Operations Dashboards to standardize the definition of application operations success across GE Gas Power.
- Created an automatic Natural Language Processing (NLP) classifier for application incidents, changes, and requests which increased the efficiency of ticket and application problem identification.
- Created an Automatic Application Verifier to on-demand and quickly check the web statuses of critical apps during vulnerable events.
- Worked with a GE Global Research Center Team to use a Zero-Shot BART Model to make a binary decision on information requests.

Department of Computer Science, UNC

Chapel Hill, NC

Research Assistant (RA)

August 2020 – Present

- Used NLP models to research for sustainability and social good applications.
- Integrated knowledge graphs with social media datasets to be used in the training of models.
- Lead and participated in a weekly undergraduate reading group focusing on current Computer Science Research.

Department of Computer Science, UNC

Chapel Hill, NC

Teaching Assistant (TA)

January 2020 - Present

- Organized a team of twelve other Teaching Assistants to create curriculum for the class.
- Conducted the selection and onboarding of new TAs.
- Held classes and office hours for ~200 students each semester.
- Graded homework, programming assignments, exams, and hardware labs.

Ruffalo Noel Levitz, LLC at the UNC Engagement Center

Chapel Hill, NC

Shift Supervisor, former Development Representative

January 2019 – August 2020

- Oversaw the collection of approximately \$1M worth of donations while managing a team of ~25 employees.
- As a Development Representative, raised \$50,000 by calling UNC alumni and parents.
- Actively recruited, interviewed, and trained team members.

Skills

Language Skills: Spanish (Intermediate), Danish (Basic)

Computer Skills: Java, C/C++, Python, Html/CSS, TypeScript, Swift, Git/GitHub, Linux/Unix, Vim, MatLab, Microsoft Office Suites, Tableau Desktop, Tableau Server